[{"answer": "Well", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I guess", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "About what", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What about it", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What about it", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "To be what", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Excuse me.  Mr. my frien", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yes, sir", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yes I am", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Mrs. my friend, will you forgive me for what I just said", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It's not all right, it's the worst thing I've ever said to anyone", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No, I don't.  But I just feel a little funny", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I know that.  But I'm", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Of course he does.  But he might get the wrong idea. Anyone might", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "But they would!  Don't you see", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Why is it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I know that.  But please, Mrs. my friend.  This is difficult for me", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Because I am confused about things.  I can't tell what I'm imagining.  I can't tell what's real.  I can't", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I have to go now.  I'm sorry", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Thank you very much, sir", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Twenty.  I'll be twent", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Look", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "- and I was wondering if I could buy you a drink or something", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Where are you", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Where are you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You?  Oh no.  No.  I'll get it", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Do you want me to get it", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Do you want to get it now", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Why don't I get it?  Well", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What?  No.  Nothing", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Luggage?  Yes.  Yes.  I do", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Is this", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "my friend, is this your first time", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "It is, isn't it?  It is your first time", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "You can admit that, can't you", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "It's nothing to be ashamed of", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Wait a minute", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Who said it was my first time", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "When I go off", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "When I go off", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "No, I do.  I want to tell you", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Oh, no", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Meet someone", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Because I know you don't drive around for twelve hours", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Not if you don't want to", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Oh.  Well, I don't.  Shall I tell you what I do", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I do", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "I don't", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "No.  Think of another topic. Tell me what you did today", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Yes I do", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "I don't remember", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "How do you get out of the house", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "You walk right out the door", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "You have not slept with your husband for five years", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "How many times a year", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "On New Year's Eve.  Sometimes on his birthday", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Is it", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Not exactly", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "No, my friend.  I don't hate him. Unhook my blouse", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Why are you asking me all this", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Because I'm interested, Mrs. my friend. Now what was your major subject at college", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Art", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Don't you expect me to be a little hurt", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Mrs. my friend, you stand there and tell me I'm not good enough for your daughter", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "Of course you did", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "I do", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Because I wouldn't want you to do it unless you really wanted to", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "You do", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "I do", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "No.  I think you'll want to wait on that", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "No", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "They don't know", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "Well", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "No.  I want to know why you're here in that place", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "Is it because I'm here", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "Is it because I'm here", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "I think it is", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "Did you say rape her", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": "When", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": "How about tomorrow?  I don't mean to be pushy but", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": "Or this afternoon.  It's a good day for it", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "We'll need our Birth Certificates. I happen to have mine with me. Where's yours", "qsentId": 102}, {"answer": "Is there something I've said that's caused this contempt?  Or is it just the things I stand for that you despise", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 105, "question": "Well, my friend, it was quite a bit to do with me", "qsentId": 104}, {"answer": "I am trying to tell you I have no personal feelings about you, Mr. my friend.  I am trying to tell you I do not resent you", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 107, "question": "No, I don't", "qsentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think we have a whole lot to say to each other, my friend.  I do think you should know the consequences of what you've done.  I do think you should know that my wife and I are getting a divorce soon", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 109, "question": "Why", "qsentId": 108}, {"answer": "That's quite a statement", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 111, "question": "Shaking hands.  Well, that's not saying much for my wife, is it", "qsentId": 110}, {"answer": "65", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 113, "question": "This is Dr. my friend's answering service", "qsentId": 112}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Graduate_-The.txt", "asentId": 115, "question": "Is the doctor anywhere", "qsentId": 114}]